Rare Pamphlet Collection 6034
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Box: 30, Folder: 20, Publication (Box 30, Folder 20)
  - Item 1: Woman of yesterday and to-day, 1915; Publication (Box 30, Folder 20)
    Author: Theresa Serber Malkiel
- Box: 30, Folder: 21, Publication (Box 30, Folder 21)
  - Item 1: Building industrial morale through human relations, 1945; Publication (Box 30, Folder 21)
    Author: A. O. Malmberg
    Notes: Address before the Sales Executives' Club of New York, Roosevelt Hotel, Jan. 31, 1945.
- Box: 30, Folder: 22, Publication (Box 30, Folder 22)
  - Item 1: Are wages too high?, 1922; Publication (Box 30, Folder 22)
    Author: Basil Maxwell Manly
- Box: 30, Folder: 23, Publication (Box 30, Folder 23)
  - Item 1: What a compulsory 8 hour working day means to the workers, 1972; Publication (Box 30, Folder 23)
    Author: Tom Mann
  - Item 2: The eight hours movement, 1889; Publication (Box 30, Folder 23)
- Box: 30, Folder: 24, Publication (Box 30, Folder 24)
  - Item 1: Women who work in New York, 1941; Publication (Box 30, Folder 24)
    Author: New York (State). Division of Women in Industry and Minimun Wage
    Notes: New York State Department of Labor, Frieda S. Miller, Industrial Commissioner. Division of Women in Industry and Minimum Wage, Kate Papert, Director.
- Box: 30, Folder: 25, Publication (Box 30, Folder 25)
  - Item 1: Shop talks on economics, 1911; Publication (Box 30, Folder 25)
    Author: Mary Marcy
- Box: 30, Folder: 26, Publication (Box 30, Folder 26)
  - Item 1: Marine labor union leadership, 1925; Publication (Box 30, Folder 26)
    Author: Walter J. Petersen
- Box: 30, Folder: 27, Publication (Box 30, Folder 27)
  - Item 1: Ashcan the M-plan, 1940; Publication (Box 30, Folder 27)
    Author: Mike Quin
  - Item 2: The Yanks are not coming, 1940; Publication (Box 30, Folder 27)
- Box: 30, Folder: 28, Publication (Box 30, Folder 28)
  - Item 1: Working less but enjoying it more: a guide to splitting or sharing your job, 1978; Publication (Box 30, Folder 28)
    Author: Barney Olmsted; Marcia Markels
- Box: 30, Folder: 29, Publication (Box 30, Folder 29)
  - Item 1: Biro Bidjan as I saw it, 1934; Publication (Box 30, Folder 29)
    Author: Dudley Leigh Aman Marley
- Box: 31, Folder: 1, Publication (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Union social services and women's work, 1985; Publication (Box 31, Folder 1)
    Author: George T. Martin
- Box: 31, Folder: 2, Publication (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: The state and the socialist revolution, 1938; Publication (Box 31, Folder 2)
    Author: L. Martov
- Box: 31, Folder: 3, Publication (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: The epic of the Black Sea revolt, 1941; Publication (Box 31, Folder 3)
    Author: Andre Marty
- Box: 31, Folder: 4, Publication (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Manifesto of the Communist Party, 1932; Publication (Box 31, Folder 4)
    Author: Karl Marx; Friedrich Engels
    Notes: Authorized English translation, edited and annotated by Friedrich Engels.
  - Item 2: The civil war in France, 1900; Publication (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - Item 3: Wage-labor and capital, 1935; Publication (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - Item 4: The Gotha program. Did Marx err?, 1922; Publication (Box 31, Folder 4)
    Author: Karl Marx; Daniel De Leon
  - Item 5: Manifesto of the Communist Party, 1948; Publication (Box 31, Folder 4)
    Author: Karl Marx; Friedrich Engels; Samuel Moore
    Notes: Authorized English translation [by Samuel Moore]; edited and annotated by Frederick Engels.
- Box: 31, Folder: 5, Publication (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Wage-labour and capital, 1935; Publication (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - Item 2: Karl Marx or Thomas Jefferson?, 1931; Publication (Box 31, Folder 5)
    Author: Charles Solomon; George Gordon Battle; Norman Thomas
    Notes: Debate on individualism-socialism between Hon. Charles Solomon and Hon. George Gordon Battle; foreword by Norman Thomas.
- Box: 31, Folder: 6, Publication (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Political economy, Publication (Box 31, Folder 6)
    Author: Marxist study courses; course 1
    Notes: Lessons 1-9
- Box: 31, Folder: 7, Publication (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: History of the working class, 1934; Publication (Box 31, Folder 7)
    Author: Marxist study courses; course 2
    Notes: Lessons 1-4
- Box: 31, Folder: 8, Publication (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: The forty-eight hours week: a years experiment and its results at the Salford iron works, Manchester, 1894; Publication (Box 31, Folder 8)
    Author: William Mather
- Box: 31, Folder: 9, Publication (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Notes on the theory of progress, 1951; Publication (Box 31, Folder 9)
    Author: Leland Mathis
- Box: 31, Folder: 10, Publication (Box 31, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: Our strike-breaking governments, 1922; Publication (Box 31, Folder 10)
    Author: James H. Maurer
  - Item 2: Employers are organized why not workers?, Publication (Box 31, Folder 10)
- Box: 31, Folder: 11, Publication (Box 31, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: What is happening in Bulgaria, 1925; Publication (Box 31, Folder 11)
    Author: Karl Maus
- Box: 31, Folder: 12, Publication (Box 31, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: May Day, 1938: for democracy, jobs, security, peace!, Publication (Box 31, Folder 12)
    Author: Alan Max
- Box: 31, Folder: 13, Publication (Box 31, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: Out of your pocket: the story of cartels, 1946; Publication (Box 31, Folder 13)
    Author: Darel McConkey; Harley M. Kilgore
- Box: 32, Folder: 1, Publication (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Bombs over Barcelona: prevent this now!!, 1938; Publication (Box 32, Folder 1)
    Author: Medical Bureau and North American Committee to Aid Spanish Democracy
- Box: 32, Folder: 2, Publication (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Southern labor in revolt, 1930; Publication (Box 32, Folder 2)
    Author: Kenneth Meiklejohn; Peter Nehemkis
- Box: 32, Folder: 3, Publication (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Socialism and the woman, Publication (Box 32, Folder 3)
    Author: Edmund T. Melms
- Box: 32, Folder: 4, Publication (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: History of the League for industrial right, 1925; Publication (Box 32, Folder 4)
    Author: Walter Gordon Merritt
  - Item 2: Social control of industrial warfare, Publication (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - Item 3: Factory solidarity or class solidarity?, Publication (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - Item 4: Issues in the Anthracite strike of 1925, Publication (Box 32, Folder 4)
- Box: 32, Folder: 5, Publication (Box 32, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Is there enough manpower?, 1942; Publication (Box 32, Folder 5)
    Author: Harold William Metz
- Box: 32, Folder: 6, Publication (Box 32, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: History in the making, 1948; Publication (Box 32, Folder 6)
    Author: Max Meyer
- Box: 32, Folder: 7, Publication (Box 32, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Just wages and salaries: minimum annual wage $3,500, 1948; Publication (Box 32, Folder 7)
    Author: Raymond J. Miller
- Box: 32, Folder: 8, Publication (Box 32, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: The ideals of labor, 1926; Publication (Box 32, Folder 8)
    Author: Spencer Miller
- Box: 32, Folder: 9, Publication (Box 32, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: How powerful is labor leadership?, 1949; Publication (Box 32, Folder 9)
    Author: C. Wright Mills; Joel Seidman; Lee C. Shaw
    Notes: NBC Radio discussion by C. Wright Mills, Joel Seidman and Lee C. Shaw.
- Box: 32, Folder: 10, Publication (Box 32, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: The fur industry, 1927; Publication (Box 32, Folder 10)
    Author: David C. Mills
- Box: 32, Folder: 11, Publication (Box 32, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: The Negro worker's progress in Minnesota, 1949; Publication (Box 32, Folder 11)
    Author: Minnesota. Governor's Interracial Commission.
    Notes: Report to Governor Luther W. Youngdahl of Minnesota
- Box: 32, Folder: 12, Publication (Box 32, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: The struggle against war: and the peace policy of the Soviet Union, 1936; Publication (Box 32, Folder 12)
    Author: Robert Minor
  - Item 2: Tell the people how Ben Davis was elected, 1946; Publication (Box 32, Folder 12)
  - Item 3: Free Earl Browder!, 1941; Publication (Box 32, Folder 12)
- Box: 32, Folder: 13, Publication (Box 32, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: The fascist menace in the U.S.A., 1934; Publication (Box 32, Folder 13)
    Author: Richard Bransten; Bruce Minton
- Box: 32, Folder: 14, Publication (Box 32, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: The Role of the U.S. Department of Labor in Foreign Affairs, 1960; Publication (Box 32, Folder 14)
- Box: 32, Folder: 15, Publication (Box 32, Folder 15)
  - Item 1: Does Norwegian labor seek the middle way?, 1937; Publication (Box 32, Folder 15)
    Author: Finn Moe
- Box: 32, Folder: 16, Publication (Box 32, Folder 16)
  - Item 1: The Protection of labour in the U.S.S.R., 1933; Publication (Box 32, Folder 16)
    Author: Z. Mokhov
  - Item 2: Lessons of the wrecking, diversionist and espionage activities of the Japanese-German-Trotskyite agents, 1937; Publication (Box 32, Folder 16)
    Author: Vyacheslav Mikhaylovich Molotov
- Box: 32, Folder: 17, Publication (Box 32, Folder 17)
  - Item 1: Monopoly in the United States, 1942; Publication (Box 32, Folder 17)
- Box: 32, Folder: 18, Publication (Box 32, Folder 18)
  - Item 1: The Avery Formula, 1944; Publication (Box 32, Folder 18)
    Author: Montgomery Ward Workers of Chicago
- Box: 32, Folder: 19, Publication (Box 32, Folder 19)
  - Item 1: Justice is waiting, 1930; Publication (Box 32, Folder 19)
    Author: Thomas J. Mooney
- Box: 32, Folder: 20, Publication (Box 32, Folder 20)
  - Item 1: Woman, her quality, her environment, her possibility, 1901; Publication (Box 32, Folder 20)
    Author: Martha Moore Avery
- Box: 32, Folder: 21, Publication (Box 32, Folder 21)
  - Item 1: More than on steel, 1930; Publication (Box 32, Folder 21)
    Author: Lynd Ward
- Box: 32, Folder: 22, Publication (Box 32, Folder 22)
  - Item 1: The Wisconsin plan of unemployment insurance, 1928; Publication (Box 32, Folder 22)
    Author: E. W. Morehouse
- Box: 32, Folder: 23, Publication (Box 32, Folder 23)
  - Item 1: A tale of two waterfronts, 1952; Publication (Box 32, Folder 23)
    Author: George Morris
  - Item 2: Conspiracy to Strangle Labor, 1951; Publication (Box 32, Folder 23)
  - Item 3: The Red baiting racket and how it works, 1948; Publication (Box 32, Folder 23)
  - Item 4: The C.I.O. today, 1950; Publication (Box 32, Folder 23)
  - Item 5: The painting scandal: District Council 9 members deserve a better deal, 1965; Publication (Box 32, Folder 23)
- Box: 32, Folder: 24, Publication (Box 32, Folder 24)
  - Item 1: Union and non-union shop, Publication (Box 32, Folder 24)
    Author: Frank Morrison
- Box: 32, Folder: 25, Publication (Box 32, Folder 25)
  - Item 1: An easy outline of modern socialism, 1940; Publication (Box 32, Folder 25)
    Author: Herbert Morrison
- Box: 32, Folder: 26, Publication (Box 32, Folder 26)
  - Item 1: Public works or public charity?: how to meet the labor crisis arising from the demobilization of troops and war workers, 1919; Publication (Box 32, Folder 26)
    Author: Harold Glenn Moulton
  - Item 2: The thirty-hour week, 1935; Publication (Box 32, Folder 26)
    Author: Harold Glenn Moulton; Maurice Leven
- Box: 32, Folder: 27, Publication (Box 32, Folder 27)
  - Item 1: Move on!: thirty thousand clothing workers on the go, Publication (Box 32, Folder 27)
- Box: 33, Folder: 1, Publication (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Some aspects of the labor problem, 1898; Publication (Box 33, Folder 1)
    Author: Philip S. Moxom
- Box: 33, Folder: 2, Publication (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Co-partnership organisation of labour, 1915; Publication (Box 33, Folder 2)
    Author: E. W. Mundy
- Box: 33, Folder: 3, Publication (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: In defense of democracy, 1940; Publication (Box 33, Folder 3)
    Author: Frank Murphy
- Box: 33, Folder: 4, Publication (Box 33, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: The workers' committee: an outline of its principles and structure, 1918; Publication (Box 33, Folder 4)
    Author: J. T. Murphy
- Box: 33, Folder: 5, Publication (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: The automobile industry and organized labor, 1936; Publication (Box 33, Folder 5)
    Author: Abraham John Muste
  - Item 2: I. The kind of unionism that will not organize the basic industries. II. The kind of unionism that will organize the basic industries. III. The organization of the textile industry., 1927; Publication (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - Item 3: The South as labor's battleground, 1929; Publication (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - Item 4: Wage peace now!, 1942; Publication (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - Item 5: Fellowship and class struggle, 1930; Publication (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - Item 6: Peace or pep? ... Whose job?, 1928; Publication (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - Item 7: Which party for the American worker?, 1935; Publication (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - Item 8: Why a labor party...and the folly of the non-partisan policy, 1929; Publication (Box 33, Folder 5)
- Box: 33, Folder: 6, Publication (Box 33, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: What the Constitution says today; a rearrangement of the Constitution of the United States, 1955; Publication (Box 33, Folder 6)
    Author: Alan Robert Murray
    Notes: The exact words of the Constitution, including the amendments, grouped by subjects, together with texts in full and names of signers of the Declaration of independence, the Articles of confederation, the Constitution of the United States and its amendment
- Box: 33, Folder: 7, Publication (Box 33, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Organized labor and consumer cooperation, 1940; Publication (Box 33, Folder 7)
    Author: James Myers
- Box: 33, Folder: 8, Publication (Box 33, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: The name is Lewis-John L., czar of the U.M.W.A, servant of the big coal interests; an example of an A. F. of L. leader., Publication (Box 33, Folder 8)
    Author: Tom Myerscough
- Box: 33, Folder: 9, Publication (Box 33, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: The NLRB coloring book, Publication (Box 33, Folder 9)
- Box: 33, Folder: 10, Publication (Box 33, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: Answer please! Questions for communists., 1950; Publication (Box 33, Folder 10)
    Author: Siegfried Nacht; Stephen Naft
  - Item 2: 100 questions to the communists, 1939; Publication (Box 33, Folder 10)
- Box: 33, Folder: 11, Publication (Box 33, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: The name is Hoffa: a profile of Detroits James R. Hoffa, vice-president of the International Brotherhood of Teamsters., 1956; Publication (Box 33, Folder 11)
    Author: Teamsters Joint Council No. 13
- Box: 33, Folder: 12, Publication (Box 33, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: Memories of building the UAW, 1976; Publication (Box 33, Folder 12)
    Author: J. S. Napier
- Box: 33, Folder: 13, Publication (Box 33, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: How about a decent school for me?: racial inequalities in education, 1946; Publication (Box 33, Folder 13)
    Author: National Association for the Advancement of Colored People
  - Item 2: Thirteen years after 1954, 1967; Publication (Box 33, Folder 13)
    Author: Alex Poinsett
  - Item 3: NAACP: victory in Mississippi, 1969; Publication (Box 33, Folder 13)
- Box: 33, Folder: 14, Publication (Box 33, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: The law of the Debs case: constitutional construction by the Supreme Court., Publication (Box 33, Folder 14)
    Author: National Civil Liberties Bureau
  - Item 2: Ol' rags an' bottles, 1919; Publication (Box 33, Folder 14)
- Box: 33, Folder: 15, Publication (Box 33, Folder 15)
  - Item 1: America's Tribute, 1942; Publication (Box 33, Folder 15)
    Author: National Committee
    Notes: Excerpt from remarks at the funeral services of Mr. Justice Brandeis, October 7, 1941, Wash., D.C.
- Box: 33, Folder: 16, Publication (Box 33, Folder 16)
  - Item 1: Red-ucators at Yale University, 1949; Publication (Box 33, Folder 16)
    Author: National Council for American Education
- Box: 33, Folder: 17, Publication (Box 33, Folder 17)
  - Item 1: Rights, Publication (Box 33, Folder 17)
    Author: National Emergency Civil Liberties Committee
    Notes: v.2:no.6,9 (1955); v.7:no.3 (1960)
- Box: 33, Folder: 18, Publication (Box 33, Folder 18)
  - Item 1: Economic situation and the struggle: outline and guide for schools, classes, study groups, 1949; Publication (Box 33, Folder 18)
    Author: National Education Department, Communist Party
- Box: 33, Folder: 19, Publication (Box 33, Folder 19)
  - Item 1: The platform of the class struggle; national platform of the Workers (communist) party, 1928; Publication (Box 33, Folder 19)
    Author: National election campaign committee
- Box: 33, Folder: 20, Publication (Box 33, Folder 20)
  - Item 1: Working women and the elections, 1932; Publication (Box 33, Folder 20)
- Box: 33, Folder: 21, Publication (Box 33, Folder 21)
  - Item 1: Report on economic conditions of the South, 1938; Publication (Box 33, Folder 21)
    Author: National Emergency Council (U.S.)
- Box: 33, Folder: 22, Publication (Box 33, Folder 22)
  - Item 1: Investigate Martin Dies!: the case for a grand jury investigation of Martin Dies, 1942; Publication (Box 33, Folder 22)
    Author: National Federation for Constitutional Liberties
    Notes: Submitted to the Department of Justice on August 6, 1942 by the National Federation for Constitutional Liberties.
- Box: 33, Folder: 23, Publication (Box 33, Folder 23)
  - Item 1: Women's wages and the cost of living, 1922; Publication (Box 33, Folder 23)
    Author: Ohio Council on Women and Children in Industry
  - Item 2: From grandmother to you and me: an introduction to the study of the 8-hour day., Publication (Box 33, Folder 23)
    Author: Women in Industry Committee of the National League of Women Voters
  - Item 3: Program of work for the National League of Women Voters, 1925-1926, Publication (Box 33, Folder 23)
    Author: National League of Women Voters (U.S.)
    Notes: Adopted in convention at Richmond, Virginia, April, 1925.
  - Item 4: Jobs and workers, 1923; Publication (Box 33, Folder 23)
- Box: 33, Folder: 24, Publication (Box 33, Folder 24)
  - Item 1: National lockout and Shrewsbury lock-in: the face of class struggle today, 1975; Publication (Box 33, Folder 24)
- Box: 33, Folder: 25, Publication (Box 33, Folder 25)
  - Item 1: International unity of the world's trade union movement, 1924; Publication (Box 33, Folder 25)
    Author: National Minority Movement
  - Item 2: Strike strategy and tactics, Publication (Box 33, Folder 25)
- Box: 33, Folder: 26, Publication (Box 33, Folder 26)
  - Item 1: Negro workers after the war, 1945; Publication (Box 33, Folder 26)
    Author: National Negro Congress (U.S.)
  - Item 2: Jim Crow in national defense, 1941; Publication (Box 33, Folder 26)
- Box: 33, Folder: 27, Publication (Box 33, Folder 27)
  - Item 1: The President's reemployment program, 1933; Publication (Box 33, Folder 27)
- Box: 33, Folder: 28, Publication (Box 33, Folder 28)
  - Item 1: Social vision for the church and labor, 1948; Publication (Box 33, Folder 28)
    Author: National Religion and Labor Foundation
- Box: 33, Folder: 29, Publication (Box 33, Folder 29)
  - Item 1: Scottish miners' delegation to Czechoslovakia, 1951; Publication (Box 33, Folder 29)
    Author: National Union of Mineworkers. Scottish Area
    Notes: August- September 1951
  - Item 2: Scottish miners' delegation to Poland, 1949; Publication (Box 33, Folder 29)
- Box: 33, Folder: 30, Publication (Box 33, Folder 30)
  - Item 1: Poland 1950: a report of a visit by a delegation pf South Wales Miners, Publication (Box 33, Folder 30)
    Author: National Union of Mineworkers. South Wales Area.
- Box: 33, Folder: 31, Publication (Box 33, Folder 31)
  - Item 1: They crashed the color line!, 1937; Publication (Box 33, Folder 31)
    Author: National Urban League. Dept. of Industrial Relations
- Box: 34, Folder: 1, Publication (Box 34, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Facts to fight with for Wallace and the new party, 1948; Publication (Box 34, Folder 1)
    Author: National Wallace for President Committee
- Box: 34, Folder: 2, Publication (Box 34, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: World labor unity, 1926; Publication (Box 34, Folder 2)
    Author: Scott Nearing
  - Item 2: Russia turns east; the triumph of soviet diplomacy in Asia, 1926; Publication (Box 34, Folder 2)
  - Item 3: British labor bids for power; The historic Scarboro Conference of the Trades Union Congress, 1926; Publication (Box 34, Folder 2)
  - Item 4: Glimpses of the Soviet Republic, 1926; Publication (Box 34, Folder 2)
  - Item 5: An A B C of Communism, Publication (Box 34, Folder 2)
  - Item 6: Labor and the league of nations, 1919; Publication (Box 34, Folder 2)
  - Item 7: The great madness, 1917; Publication (Box 34, Folder 2)
  - Item 8: The one big union of business, 1920; Publication (Box 34, Folder 2)
  - Item 9: Oil and the germs of war, 1923; Publication (Box 34, Folder 2)
  - Item 10: The one way out (Rev. ed.), 1933; Publication (Box 34, Folder 2)
  - Item 11: The one way out: an answer to hard times, 1932; Publication (Box 34, Folder 2)
- Box: 34, Folder: 3, Publication (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: The Debs decision, 1919; Publication (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - Item 2: World labor unity, 1926; Publication (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - Item 3: The rise and decline of Christian civilization, 1940; Publication (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - Item 4: Work and pay, 1917; Publication (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - Item 5: Who owns the United States?, Publication (Box 34, Folder 3)
- Box: 34, Folder: 4, Publication (Box 34, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Profit sharing, 1887; Publication (Box 34, Folder 4)
    Author: N. O. Nelson
- Box: 34, Folder: 5, Publication (Box 34, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: War again to-morrow!, 1933; Publication (Box 34, Folder 5)
    Author: Nemo
- Box: 34, Folder: 6, Publication (Box 34, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: European trade unionism and politics, 1936; Publication (Box 34, Folder 6)
    Author: Franz L. Neumann; Carl Raushenbush; Harold J. Laski
- Box: 34, Folder: 7, Publication (Box 34, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Constitution and by-laws of the New York Council, 1894; Publication (Box 34, Folder 7)
    Author: New York (State). Council of Mediation and Conciliation
- Box: 34, Folder: 8, Publication (Box 34, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Starvation wages, awful living conditions and state charity insurance go hand-in-hand in Germany: American labor is suspicious of those who would fasten the hand of government upon the workers of this country., 1918; Publication (Box 34, Folder 8)
    Author: New York League for Americanism
  - Item 2: Labor's attitude towards compulsory state health insurance (known in Germany as Reichskranken-Versicherung), 1919; Publication (Box 34, Folder 8)
- Box: 34, Folder: 9, Publication (Box 34, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Towards a militant program for the Socialist Party of America, 1934; Publication (Box 34, Folder 9)
- Box: 34, Folder: 10, Publication (Box 34, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: The NMU fights Jim Crow, 1943; Publication (Box 34, Folder 10)
    Author: National Maritime Union of America
- Box: 34, Folder: 11, Publication (Box 34, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: Women who work in New York, 1941; Publication (Box 34, Folder 11)
- Box: 34, Folder: 12, Publication (Box 34, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: Report and protest to the governor, the Legislature and the people of the State of New York, danger confronting popular government, the Daly lobby and propaganda, and the so-called New York League for Americanism, a powerful and perilous influence, 1920; Publication (Box 34, Folder 12)
    Author: New York State League of Women Voters
- Box: 34, Folder: 13, Publication (Box 34, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: How management can integrate Negroes in war industries, 1942; Publication (Box 34, Folder 13)
    Author: John A. Davis
  - Item 2: The Negro integrated, 1945; Publication (Box 34, Folder 13)
    Author: New York State War Council
- Box: 34, Folder: 14, Publication (Box 34, Folder 14)